[Music]
[Música]
so they do what they do
para que se dedican a lo que se dedican
on TV, yes, to watch, but this is how it
a la tele que sí a ver pero esto es como
usually happens, I mean, remember also
suele pasar o sea recuerda también el
Antonio's little bite, there was Marta Reyes
bocadito de Antonio había Marta Reyes
with the factory, which was one of the
con la fábrica que ahí era una de las
TV factories, it was wonderful
fábricas de la tele fue maravilloso
when that video came out, but
cuando salió la luz ese vídeo pero yo
well, look, Javi, I'll tell you one thing when
pues mira Javi te digo una cosa cuando
the video lights came out, I already knew, I
salió la luces de vídeo yo ya lo sabía o
mean, I already knew that what I want to tell you that, well,
sea yo ya sabía que que te quiero decir
something, well, I had already
que pues que algo pues que yo ya había
heard about those images and I had
escuchado hablar de esas imágenes y
heard about that subject, but
había escuchado hablar de ese tema pero
long before, uh, I don't know, much, much,
mucho antes eh No sé mucho mucho
well, you can say that they were
había bueno puedes decir que se estén
betting on each other, but maybe there was already
apostando pero a lo mejor que existía ya
a tension, I think there was an
una tensión creo que asistía hay una
attraction, a flirtation,
atracción un tonteo
I think Antonio David has always
yo creo que Antonio David siempre
been a person who
también ha sido una persona que le gusta
really likes to like, and Marta has always
mucho gustar y a Marta siempre le ha
loved Antonio David, like, Hey, a
encantado Antonio David en plan como Oye
guy you really like, she's always
un tío que te gusta mucho siempre ha
been in love, or excited, or infatuated
estado enamorada o ilusionada o embobada
with him, always, I mean, since, I think that, they
con siempre o sea desde yo creo que sí
also meet at parties and the
además se encuentran en las fiestas y el
other one, well, to put himself in a position to pat
otro pues para ponerse así en plan para
himself on the back for looking for him, he
echarse flores a sí mismo por buscarlo
liked it, well, there  there was a teacher that ca
le gustaba pues ahí hubo un maestro eso
n't be justified in that video he
no se puede justificar en ese vídeo le
threw him some bites a flirting you know how
lanzó un bocaditos un tonteo sabes como
come on let's go where do I do the girls with the
venga vamos donde hago las niñas con la
reporter
reportera
but
pero
as I saw the other day there was Amador
como he visto el otro día había Amador
smoking that I mean well here you can smoke
fumar eso o sea pues aquí se puede fumar
for sure no they don't tell you anything yes
seguro no que no te dicen nada que sí
all the live shows you ask it You
todos los directos lo preguntas tú Tú
can do what you want I
puedes hacer lo que tú quieras
read a comment or so the other day
he leído un comentario o sea el otro día
from people of don't smoke how do you smoke I mean Hey
de gente de no fumes como fumas digo Oye
I'm not killing anyone that the whole drama in life is smoking for God's sake of course let's see it's that we are very against tobacco you shouldn't smoke it's family But man if you smoke and are more comfortable smoking but I don't prohibit it nobody like like let's see you know
sea en plan A ver tú sabes
in front of the whole company of unicor
delante de toda la empresa de unicor
here several increase one that the
aquí varias incrementar uno que ellos
two of them do it in front of the whole company
dos lo hagan delante de toda la empresa
of unique because one thing is that it gets out
de único porque una cosa es que se te
of hand from flirting but
vaya de las manos del tonteo pero
normally when you're doing something like that
normalmente cuando estás haciendo algo
bad I
así malo
understand that you want to hide no I mean
entiendo que te querrás ocultar no O sea
you don't care because I mean you're so
te da igual porque o sea estás tan
horny and you're losing so much
caliente y estás perdiendo tanto el
control with the drink that you don't know that you
control con la bebida que no sabes que
're with all your colleagues
estás con todos tus compañeros de
Telecinco from your production company in the same
telecinco de tu productora en el mismo
venue And then point number 2 Marina
recinto Y luego el punto número 2 Marina
broadcast images of a private party in
emitir imágenes de una fiesta privada en
a private venue, they have
un local privado a mí me han llegado a
sent me videos of very very very very very very very famous youtubers
mandar vídeos de youtubers muy muy muy
doing things like flirting and
haciendo cosas en plan de ligoteos y
things in
cosas en
clubs and I have not taken the risk You know
discotecas y yo no me la he jugado Sabes
because let's see it is a place even maybe
porque a ver es un sitio incluso a lo
nothing can happen to you because it is
mejor no te puede pasar nada porque es
a place to see You are in a [ __ ]
un sitio a ver Estás en una [__]
club with hundreds of people if you
discoteca con cientos de personas si
do something there handsome or watch out for the
haces algo ahí guapo o atenta las
consequences But I don't know it is very
consecuencias Pero no sé es muy
there are indications that would make me think
hay indicios que a mí me darían a pensar
that I would not rule out a setup
que yo no descartaría un montaje
and so many cameras Marina because there are at
y tantas cámara Marina porque son por lo
least four or five different videos
menos cuatro o cinco vídeos diferentes
from several cameras
de varias cámaras
well in the program they said a 20 is
bueno en el programa dijeron una 20 está
recording there I don't know but look look
grabando ahí no sé pero mira mira
independently of this matter itself
independientemente de este asunto en sí
What is true is that I believe that there are
Lo que sí es verdad que yo creo que hay
many people of these 4,120 people who
mucha gente de estas 4.120 personas que
are here surely more than one will say
están aquí seguro que más de una dirá
Look I can get more indignant I could
Mira me puedo indignar más podría
find Alba against the other I can
encontrar de Alba en contra del otro
but don't tell me that on the one hand it
pueda pero no me digáis que por un lado
is not a little peace of saying
no es un poco paz de decir
hurricane Rocío Carrasco  Paz stop and we give
huracán Rocío Carrasco Paz stop y damos
that there were other topics behind and that seems like
que había otros temas atrás y eso parece
nonsense but it's like a little
una chorrada pero es como un poco de
break from the other and look now there are
descanso de lo otro y mira ahora hay
other topics the Bernardo Pantoja topic
otros temas el tema de Bernardo Pantoja
this topic and I sincerely am
este tema y a mí me sinceramente me
happy Although it makes me a little angry but I'm
alegra Aunque me indigne un poco pero ya
not so angry anymore, I'm sure that people
no me indigno tanto seguro que la gente
will say the same thing Thank goodness because it was already
dirá lo mismo Menos mal porque ya
a little tiring or not a little tiring it's that it
cansaba un poco o no cansaba un poco es
exhausted let's
que agotaba
see I think that it's a topic that will
a ver yo creo que es un tema que no se
never end look for example we are going
va acabar nunca mirará por ejemplo vamos
to talk about the interview each Marta,
a hablar de la entrevista cada Marta
surely about Marta Antonio David Olga I do
seguro que de Marta Antonio David Olga
n't know about the one on the motorcycle there will surely
no sé que el de la moto seguro que
always be news listen to me about the
siempre habrá noticias escúchame de la
Flores Moreno Jurado Mohedano
familia Flores Moreno Jurado mohedano
Pantoja Rivera Cayetano family we have been
Pantoja Rivera Cayetano llevamos
talking for 30 years since the 90s that
hablando 30 años desde los años 90 que
these heart programs have existed there more or less sometimes with more
estos de del corazón algunas veces con
intensity less frequently with
más intensidad con menos frecuencia con
more know what I'm telling you but in the end they
más saber lo que te digo pero al final
are the media families of Spain
son las familias mediáticas de España
are what they are then maybe there is
son las que son entonces a lo mejor hay
a time of calm because suddenly
una época de calma porque de repente
now this week this Alba Carrillo Jorge topic is more viral
ahora esta semana es más viral este tema
but maybe
de Alba Carrillo Jorge pero a lo mejor
suddenly  Marta riesgo gets
de repente Marta riesgo se queda
pregnant and tells the truth next month
embarazada y lo cuenta el mes que viene
I'm going to tell you something I want now
yo te voy a decir una cosa quiero ahora
that you just said this look the other
que acabas de decir esto mira yo el otro
day when I saw Antonio David's live show I
día cuando vi el directo de Antonio
was amazed when I see
David que estaba alucinada cuando veo
almost 15,000 people in front of me those
casi 15.000 personas cara a mí esas
things I'm very apprehensive and to me
cosas Yo es que soy muy aprensiva y a mí
those things I say oh my god 15,000 But
esas cosas digo madre mía 15.000 Pero
how outrageous And when I saw him so
qué barbaridad Y cuando le vi tan
excited three times I thought what
emocionado tres veces yo pensé que le
happens to Antonio David fit in the inside
pasa a Antonio David quepa el el intra
what is not seen beyond what he
lo que no se ve más allá de lo que
says because it's that he surprised me
cuente porque es que me ha sorprendido
because it's true that I man here we are
porque verdad que yo hombre que aquí
all human we are
todos somos humanos estamos
used to it too he has had a very
acostumbrados también ha pasado una muy
bad time seeing him maybe colder
mala temporada de verle quizá más frío
no more more stronger or bad in the end
no más más más fuerte o mal al final
each one puts on their armor it was possible but
cada uno se pone su coraza se pudo pero
I had never seen him like that on
yo no le había visto Así alguna vez en
television Yes but in an excited way
televisión Sí pero en plan emocionado
reading a message to who was a to a
leyendo un mensaje a quien era una a una
follower with the subject of his mother
seguidora con el tema de su madre
a kiss Loli huertas well
un beso Loli huertas pues pues
yesterday he was here all night with the
ayer estuvo toda la noche aquí con el
gossip but in the canijo today maybe there are
cotilleo pero en el canijo hoy a lo
several colleagues at this
mejor que hay varios compañeros a esta
time and then  the best one like this
hora y entonces a lo mejor uno como este
please None like this besides I'm
por favor Ninguno como este además Es
really telling you that when
que de verdad te digo que Cuando entró
his mother Luisa came on the live like you moved me
su madre Luisa en el directo como que me
a news it was on Sunday night
una noticia fue el domingo por la noche
I was crazy or rather but the piece of mine
estaba yo loco o sea pero el trozo mío
that was what the words that he
que fue el lo que las palabras que me
addressed to me and then to the other YouTube and such they
dirigió y luego al otro YouTube y tal me
were sending me some extracts
fueron mandando algunos extractos estaba
I was between when he arrived I washed we went to
yo entre que llegaba él me aseaba fuimos
dinner also with a couple that we
a cenar también con una pareja que
had met there in Barcelona it
habíamos quedado allí en Barcelona
's impossible a minister you have become a
es imposible un ministro te has hecho un
minister and today giving today today in the
ministro y hoy dando hoy hoy por la
morning I had the thing about the
mañana tenía lo de la lo de la
university that by the way
universidad que por cierto estaba allí
Cristina Soria was there Oh I didn't ask you
Cristina Soria Ah no te he preguntado
about that it was this morning yes this morning
por eso era esta mañana sí esta mañana
with Cristina Alberto's wife I have
con Cristina la mujer de Alberto
n't spoken to her because it was my
no he hablado con ella porque ha sido mi
interview then I went out to have
entrevista luego me salió yo a tomarme
a coffee with the rancio with Julio the
un café con el rancio con Julio el
presenter and I had the coffee with her
presentador y me tomé el café con ella
he came in that he has so many
él entró para dentro que tenga tanta
interviews I already well imitate if I left and
entrevista yo ya pues imitar si me fui y
when I came back I already had
cuando he vuelto ya me he tenido que
a call with Juan López de
tuvo una llamada con Juan López de
Zárate that we have to enter to see
Zárate que tenemos que meter para ver
how my weekend had gone and that
cómo me había ido el fin de semana y eso
called me and already  I had to exhaust myself until
me llamó y ya me tuve que agostar hasta
today he hasn't uploaded videos anywhere
hoy no subió vídeos en ningún lado
because I already needed it like
porque es que ya necesitaba como
first of all it's
primeramente
going to blow your mind yesterday you toured
te va a petar la mente ayer recorriste
half the peninsula and part of the Islands and your
media península y parte de las Islas y
mind is going to blow but that's
te va Petra la mente pero es lo que te
what I'm telling you the 15,000 viewers at least those who more or less come to mind and so on but that we get here to take this as a medium and that 15,000 no that 15,000 is little or rather that here there is the audience that there is on TV like we are Here people
tele en plan que estemos Aquí la gente
like 100,000 viewers or 200,000
como 100.000 espectadores o 200.000
viewers in each live broadcast I think
espectadores en cada directo Yo creo que
you're going to achieve it you know why
tú lo vas a conseguir sabes por qué
Because from the outside it's not that I'm
Porque yo desde fuera no es que sea yo
anyone here to say anything but you see
nadie para aquí decir nada pero se ve
when a person
cuando una persona
embraces that if you try to set up like your
abarca que si intentas montar como tu
own medium that if then a channel for
propio medio que si luego un canal para
this other for the dedication it shows
tal otro para la dedicación se nota
then for better or for worse because we
entonces para bien o para mal porque
all have our faults our
todos tenemos nuestros fallos nuestras
things but yes it's true that I believe that
cosas pero sí que es verdad que yo creo
in that line you're going to
que sí que en esa línea lo vas a
achieve it and in the end it's what we
conseguir y al final es lo que lo que
have  we've talked about setting up a
hemos hablado lo de montar un médico de
communications doctor, television is increasingly
comunicación la televisión cada vez nos
reflected in the audiences, each time we see ourselves
vemos reflejado las audiencias cada vez
reflected,
se va mermando un poco más aparecen
other platforms appear, Netflix, pay-TV,
otras plataformas Netflix de pago
YouTube, a lot of people Javi, well, it's that as a
YouTube muchísima gente Javi bueno es
result of all this, for example,
que a raíz por ejemplo de todo esto
Telecinco jar, how many people have
frasco de telecinco Cuánta gente ha
discovered YouTube, surely the
descubierto YouTube seguro que la
majority, some, many of those who are
mayoría algunos muchos de los que están
here have been as a result of, precisely because
aquí ha sido a raíz de de precisamente
of that. Hey, I see it as another way of spending
de eso Oye yo lo veo otra forma de pasar
the nights because I don't want to name the
las noches porque no quiero nombrar al
YouTuber, but it's that I see you all. I
youtuber pero es que os veo a todos O
mean, I watch a live show of one person, another, another,
sea me veo un directo de uno otro de
another, because in the end, you know, it
otro otro porque al final sabes que me
seems to me that you can also contribute
parece que también se puede aportar
much more than I think, there are
mucho más de lo que yo creo que hay
people who are great and they know it, there are people
gente que es genial y lo sabe hay gente
who don't like YouTube, there are people I say, Oh, I'm going to
que no YouTube hay gente le digo Ay voy
do a live show on YouTube and it's like
a hacer un directo de YouTube y es como
on YouTube you don't know so-and-so, you
si en YouTube no conoces a tal la cual
know, but well, I think that little by little
sabes pero bueno Yo creo que poco a poco
[Music]
[Música]